Guide to the Tamiment Library Web Archive (Labor and the Left): Economic and Social Justice TAM.599
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
Tamiment Library Web Archive (Labor and the Left): Economic and Socical Justice
2010-
TAM.599
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
0.0010 linear feet (1+ websites: i.e., a collection of websites that grows on an ongoing basis)
The Tamiment Library Web Archive (Labor and the Left): Economic and Social Justice Movements, was created with the Web Archiving Service from the California Digital Library, which was made possible with support from the National Digital Information and Infrastructure Preservation Program (Library of Congress) and the University of California, as part of a project to preserve born-digital political communication. The Tamiment Library creates topically based archives of websites documenting labor and left activity, principally that based in the United States, with a particular focus on New York City. The collection contains periodically archived web sites of entities concerned with economic and social justice, including the defense of the welfare state, that reflect a left/progressive viewpoint. NOTE: For technical, privacy and other reasons, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl.
Tamiment Library.
Historical/Biographical Note
The Tamiment Library Web Archive (Labor and the Left): Economic and Social Justice, was created with the Web Archiving Service from the California Digital Library. This service employs open source web archiving utilities developed by Internet Archive with the support of the The International Internet Preservation Consortium. The Web Archiving Service was made possible with support from the National Digital Information and Infrastructure Preservation Program and the University of California, as part of a project to preserve born-digital political communication. The role of the Tamiment Library during this project and thereafter was/is to create topically based archives of websites documenting contemporary and ongoing labor and left activity, principally that based in the United States.
Related Archival Material
A list of related Tamiment Library web archives, whose ns2:titles all begin with the prefix "Tamiment Library Web Archive (Labor and the Left), can be found at the website Web Archives from New York University Libraries
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Scope and Content Note
The Tamiment Library Web Archive (Labor and the Left): Economic and Social Justice Movements collection contains periodically archived web sites of entities concerned with economic and social justice, including the defense of the welfare state, that reflect a left/progressive viewpoint. NOTE: For technical, privacy and other reasons, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. NOTE: if a link for an individual site does not work, click on the TITLE of the collection (in the "Description" section at the beginning of the finding aid) to access this web archive, then go to the site list and select the web site(s) you wish to view.
Arrangement
Websites arranged alphabetically.
Distributive justice.; Social justice.; Social responsibility in banking.; Social responsibility of business.
- Economic and Social Justice
  - #occupywallstreet, 10/23/2011-
  - 15th October, 10/18/2011-12/1/2011
  - American Independent Business Alliance (AMIBA), 1/08/2012-
  - BanksterUSA, 7/16/2011-
  - Black Left Unity Network, 5/7/2012-
  - Campaign for America's Future, 6/12/2010-
  - Center for American Progress Action Fund, 10/6/2011-
  - Center for Popular Economics, 5/3/2011-
  - Center for the Working Poor, 3/23/2010-
  - Color of Change, 7/7/2011-
  - Committee Against Anti-Asian Violence (CAAAV), 10/25/2011-
  - Community Voices Heard, 2/3/2012-
  - Daily Occupier, 5/2/2012-
  - Demand Progress, 3/27/2012-
  - EconoMonitor: Robert Reich, 8/9/2011-
  - F (Foreclose) the Banks, 3/26/2012-
  - FirstGameWorld: Occupy Wall Street, 10/24/2011-11/27/2011
  - General Assembly at Occupy Wall Street, 10/5/2011-
  - Grassroots Global Justice Alliance, 11/09/2011-
  - Grassroots Immigrant Justice Network, 7/5/2011-
  - Highlander Research and Education Center, 6/23/2011-
  - How to Occupy, 11/11/2011-
  - I Am the 99 Percent, 11/2/2011-12/17/2011
  - Interoccupy, 12/5/2011-
  - Make Wall Street Pay, 10/12/2011-
  - May Day 2012, 4/22/2012-
  - May Day Solidarity 2012, 5/2/2012
  - Move Your Money Project, 1/06/2012-
  - The Multitude, 2/24/2012-
  - National Economic and Social Rights Initiative, 5/4/2012-
  - National Jobs For All Coalition, 5/10/2012-
  - National People's Action, 1/6/2012-
  - New Bottom Line, 2/13/2012-
  - New York City March to Washington DC, 11/10/2011-
  - Occupationalist, 11/09/2011-1/18/2012
  - Occupy Albany, 5/4/2012-
  - Occupy Colleges, 12/11/2011-
  - Occupy DC, 10/22/2011-
  - Occupy Design, 10/24/2011-
  - Occupy Guitarmy, 5/1/2012-
  - Occupy News, 12/3/2011-
  - Occupy Our Homes, 12/10/2011-
  - Occupy Pics, 12/5/2011-
  - Occupy Resistance, 12/9/2011-
  - Occupy Stories, 11/11/2011-
  - Occupy Technology, 10/25/2011-
  - Occupy the Boardroom, 11/2/2011-
  - Occupy the Bronx, 4/29/2012-
  - Occupy the Caucus, 11/12/2011-1/21/2012
  - Occupy the Nation, 10/18/2011-
  - Occupy Together, 10/6/2011-
  - Occupy Wall Street, 10/6/2011-
  - Occupy Wall Street Care Packages, 10/26/2011-12/8/2011
  - Occupy Wall Street Library, The People's Library at Liberty Plaza, 10/18/2011-
  - Occupy Wall Street Media, "Occupied Wall Street Journal", 10/26/2011-
  - Occupy Wall Street Review, 2/13/2012-
  - Occupy Washington DC, 10/24/2011-
  - Occupy Wishlist, 11/03/2011-1/19/2012
  - Occupy with Art, 12/04/2011-
  - Occupy Writers, 10/25/2011-
  - Occupy.net, 4/28/2012-
  - Occupycomix, 5/13/2012-
  - OccupyFACE, 2/14/2012-4/14/2012
  - OccupyWiki.org, 10/24/2011-1/19/2012
  - One Nation Working Together, 12/22/2010-9/23/2011
  - OneWorld, 4/22/2012-
  - Organizing for Occupation, Housing Justice in NYC through Direct Action, 10/18/2011-
  - Other 98%, 4/21/2012-
  - OWS Direct Action, 3/24/2012-
  - Parents for Occupy Wall Street, 10/23/2011-
  - People of Color / #OccupyWallStreet, 11/3/2011-
  - Philadelphia Unemployment Project, 5/5/2011-
  - Physicians for a National Health Program, 5/8/2011-
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility, 5/3/2011-
  - Picture the Homeless, 7/3/2011-
  - Public Citizen, 4/17/2010
  - Rebuild the Dream, 1/08/2012-
  - Revolution Truth, 3/29/2012-
  - Showdown in America, 10/17/2011-
  - SignOn.org, 12/9/2011-
  - smartMeme
  - Squidding, 2/11/2012
  - Take the Square, 10/7/2011-
  - U.S. PIRG, 2/03/2012-
  - Urban Justice Center, 10/17/2011-
  - US Social Forum 2010 (click on title of collection to access this website), 7/17/2010
  - We are the 99 Percent, 10/21/2011-
  - World Can't Wait!, 10/20/2011-